foreign
what is that over there floating in the
lake it looks like a person or some [ __ ]
I think so and look he's not wearing any
clothes
today must be our lucky day who wants to
rape him first
wait a minute that's not just anyone
that's Kazuki Takahashi the creator of a
Ugo
how could such a great man like a [ __ ]
the others will be so heartbroken
Joey are you okay
I'm just worried about Al Yugi will take
it he really loved take a Hashi and not
in a gay way
then let's tell him as soon as we can
come on let's hurry and finish our
baloney and cheese sandwiches
foreign
good morning everyone are you ready for
the duel monsters tournament this
evening yeah about that you we just got
some horrible news cause you could take
it ashy the man who made you give just
died they say it was found face down
flooding in the ocean as if you drowned
face down like in defense move
no you look like he's dead I get it like
he's been sent to the graveyard well
that's no big deal I play the spell card
monster reborn to bring takasha back
from the that's enough Yuki it's over
but but dual monster says I can life
isn't dual Masters Yuji Life Is Life
he's dead forever and the best thing we
can do is honor his memory when did he
die like four months ago Joey why didn't
you tell me this sooner and like me
before I send you to the shadow realm
Tristan didn't want to tell you
so this is Tristan's fault no yiki he
simply did want to hurt your feelings
well now my feelings are her Joey not
because takish eyes did but because you
my very own friend felt the need to lie
to me
till now I ask how are you going to make
it up to me perhaps by taking me to
Dairy Queen to get an ice cream con
e Dairy Queen I ain't got the money
then how about you let me [ __ ] your dark
hole
oh [ __ ]
get down [ __ ] it's time to get [ __ ]
by my Egyptian god balls
the rest of our friends were wise not to
come here otherwise they may have shared
the same fate as you
and he did attack damn it Joy you knew
this would happen but too bad for you I
was prepared for this moment as well I
play mystical space typhoon to destroy
the vegan attack blocking your dog oh
[Music]
thank you
not so fast and play card of Destruction
now you have to spend time drawing five
new cards
with pleasure
I drew another dark hole
prove it
ah [ __ ]
will you two cut it out why are you two
always doing this
I'm not doing [ __ ]
she's right Joey you might act like you
don't want it but you came prepared with
that card taped to your bottom cheeks we
must finally put an end to this fetish
forgive me my friends
that this news of tikahashadine is so
sudden it's like one you get hit by a
really strong attack in the game of Doom
monsters
yes but this isn't dual monsters Yuji
this is real life
no perhaps deep down we are all monsters
but that doesn't mean we have to be the
bad ones like the summon skull we can be
good ones too like guy of a dragon
champion
and my baby dragon
or this card
and to mind the mighty master of magic
I'm not reading that [ __ ]